{
    "subject": "resource/Lily_in_Love",
    "predicate": "http://purl.org/dc/terms/subject",
    "object": "resource/Category:Films_directed_by_K\u00e1roly_Makk",
    "human_readable": "Lily in Love is a subject of the films directed by K\u00e1roly Makk.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8966740369796753,
            "question": "Is Lily in Love a film?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8574492931365967,
            "question": "Who directed Lily in Love?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8496618866920471,
            "question": "What is the name of the film directed by K\u00e1roly Makk?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.73944091796875,
            "question": "What other films has K\u00e1roly Makk directed?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6106390953063965,
            "question": "What is the genre of Lily in Love?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5348013639450073,
            "question": "Who are the main actors in Lily in Love?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5139334201812744,
            "question": "Is K\u00e1roly Makk a Hungarian filmmaker?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5074237585067749,
            "question": "What are some themes explored in Lily in Love?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.49588537216186523,
            "question": "Where was Lily in Love filmed?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4370199143886566,
            "question": "When was Lily in Love released?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Lily in Love is a subject of the films directed by K\u00e1roly Makk.",
            "html": "dbpedia_6056_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where was Lily in Love filmed?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6056_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some themes explored in Lily in Love?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6056_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is K\u00e1roly Makk a Hungarian filmmaker?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6056_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6056_116.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6056_125.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6056_127.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6056_36.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6056_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6056_54.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6056_59.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6056_65.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6056_88.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6056_98.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{\n    \"output\": \"yes\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents mention that Karoly Makk directed \"Lily in Love,\" which supports the query."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}